(Raj:)where he says he got caught
using someone else's badge,
(Raj:)and Sheldon was right,
he did get charged with petty theft.
(Raj:)Guys, if I go to jail
dressed as the Human Torch,
(Raj:)that might send the wrong message.
(Leonard:)Maybe this isn't a good idea.
(Howard:)I can text the guy and tell him
we changed our minds.
(Raj:)Do it.
(Howard:)Okay. We're officially
not going to Comic-Con.
(Leonard:)Hold on.
We always do this.
(Howard:)-Do what?
-Chicken out.
(Leonard:)We're so afraid
of getting into trouble
(Leonard:)that we never do anything wrong.
(Raj:)That's 'cause we're the good guys.
(Leonard:)Even Batman breaks the rules.
(Raj:)You know I struggle with Batman.
(Leonard:)I say, this one time,
instead of wimping out,
let's be badasses!
(Raj:)Okay, I'll be a badass.
(Raj:)But only if you pinky-swear
to be one, too.
(Leonard:)Howard, you in on this?
(Howard:)No need.
I'm breaking rules all the time.